worldticketshop.com 2015-05-25

# Privacy Policy Worldticketshop

**WORLDTICKETSHOP.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

**INFORMATION THIS SITE GATHERS/TRACKS**  
We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. This means that although your IP address may be associated during your session, it is not permanently associated with any of your personal information.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

_Personally Identifiable Information (PII)_

We share PII with Third Parties to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, sending email and postal mail, and analyzing data for the purposes of data scrubbing and marketing assistance. We do not share PII with Third Parties for any unknown or unrelated uses. 

We reserve the right to disclose PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

_Agents_

This Web site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We employ other companies and individuals (Agents) to perform functions on our behalf. 

We use Agents to fulfill and distribute orders, to bill you for goods and services, and to assist us in marketing efforts. They have access to PII needed to perform their functions but are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing, or using PII for any other purposes.

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_

We use Third Party Service Providers to assist us in analyzing the aggregate information about the visitors on our site. This information, which helps us optimize the usability of our site, is collected via Service Provider cookie or log files. We do not link any aggregate information to PII. 

**COOKIES**  
To use our website is necessary to use cookies. Cookies are used in order to facilitate the tracking of your shopping cart, customize your future purchases, and to assist you in your needs. If you request, we may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and save your password. For that you should not re-enter it each time you visit our site. If you wish you can configure your browser to be warned when receiving cookies and refuse the use of cookies on your hard drive. Please read the instructions and manuals on your browser for more information. 

**LINKS  
**This site contains links to other sites. Worldticketshop.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read posted privacy statements whenever interacting with any Web site. We will not share any specific information that you provide to us without your explicit permission to share it. We may share broad demographic information with others. We will never release your personal information (including but not limited to your name, email address, street address, and phone number) without your express permission. Users have the ability to change their preferences with us at any time; see our Opt-Out Policy below. 

**ORDER FORM  
**This Web site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending email and postal mail, and analyzing data for the purposes of data scrubbing and marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but may not use it for other purposes. Users may opt-out of receiving communications from our company at any time; see our Opt-Out Policy below. 

**CONTESTS/PROMOTIONS**  
Occasionally, we host contests and promotions. In these contests or promotions, online or otherwise, we may ask visitors for contact information. We use this contact data to send users information regarding the specific contest or promotion. This personal information is also used to contact the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving communications from our company at any time; see our Opt-Out Policy below. 

**SECURITY**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact our [Customer Care](http://www.worldticketshop.com/contact_us)[](http://www.worldticketshop.com/contact_us)

**THIRD PARTY NOTIFICATION  
**If your personal information is ever collected by any Third Party that is not our agent/service provider, you will be notified so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

**REFERRALS**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him/her to visit the site. Worldticketshop stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. He/she may contact our [Customer Care](http://www.worldticketshop.com/contact_us)

to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**OPT-OUT POLICY  
**If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. You are not able to opt-out of emails related to a specific order (confirmation emails). 

**ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct or update it by contacting our [Customer Care](http://www.worldticketshop.com/contact_us), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**CONTACT US**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the security practices of this site, please contact: 

Worldticketshop.com  
Heresingel 4b  
9711 ES Groningen  
The Netherlands

Phone: +31 (0) 50 201 1524  
Email:

EFFECTIVE DATE: 01/31/2010
